senacases.com 2018-12-24

# Privacy Policy | Sena Cases – SENA Cases

## **We care about your privacy!**

This Privacy Policy is to inform you of our online information practices and your choices regarding the collection and use of your information. This Privacy Policy applies to all information collected from the Senacases.com website and also applies to certain other electronic information as outlined below.

### **Privacy Principles**

Sena® is committed to treating your information in accordance with law and your directions to us. “Your information” means any information about you that you or third parties provide to us.  The following commitment applies:

  * We will comply with applicable privacy and data protection laws.
  * We will only collect and use your information where we have lawful grounds and legitimate business reasons to do so.
  * We will tell you how we collect and use your information (including through this Privacy Policy).
  * We will not ask for more information than we reasonably need.
  * We will update our records when you inform us that your details have changed.
  * We will implement reasonable and appropriate information retention policies.
  * We will employ reasonable security measures to protect your information.

Other than Cookies as described below, you are not required to provide any personal information on the public areas of this website. However, you may choose to do so by completing the forms on various pages of the site. We will only use the information you provide to us on these pages in order to process the relevant form or in accordance with your consent.

For each visitor browsing our website, our web server automatically recognizes and stores the visitor's IP address (the Internet address of the visitor's computer) to determine which areas of our site is being visited and how long each visitor spends there. This information helps us to understand visitors’ traffic patterns through our website so that we can enhance the overall usability of our website. Your computer provides this information automatically each time you log on, unless you've activated blocking technology available in some browsers. While we do not generally require that you provide us with individually identifiable information in order to visit and use our website, at times we (or the third party vendors with whom we contract) may ask you to provide us with personal information such as your E-mail address, name, mailing address, telephone number, credit card number, demographic information, or persistent identifier (such as user name and password) which is associated with individually identifiable information, to enable you to make a purchase, register a product, correspond with us, enter a sweepstakes, participate in an online survey, subscribe to a mailing list or newsletter, or register for special purchase discounts. You have the right not to provide any of the requested personal information, but you may not be able to participate in some activities on this website without your personal information.

#### **Cookies**

Like many websites today, we may employ a standard technology called “cookies” to collect information about how you use our site in order to provide you with a better experience by measuring which areas of our website of greatest interest or to remember you when you return to visit us.

#### **_What are cookies?_**

A cookie is a small piece of data that a website asks your browser to store on your computer or mobile device. The cookie allows the website to “remember” your actions or preferences over time.

Most browsers support cookies, but users can set their browsers to decline them and can delete them whenever they like.

**_Websites mainly use cookies to:_**

  * identify users
  * remember users’ custom preferences
  * help users complete tasks without having to re‑enter information when browsing from one page to another or when visiting the site later

Cookies can also be used for online target advertising and to show advertisements relevant to something the user searched for in the past.

#### **_How are they used?_**

The web server supplying the webpage can store a cookie on the user’s computer or mobile device. An external web server that manages files included or referenced in the webpage is also able to store cookies. Each time the user requests a new page, the web server can receive the value of the cookies it previously set and return the page with content relating to these values.

#### **_What are the different types of cookies?_**

A cookie can be classified by its lifespan and the domain to which it belongs. By lifespan, cookies are either:

  * **a session cookie,** which is erased when the user closes the browser; this type of cookie is used, for instance, as a test to see whether or not browser settings allow cookies to be set on your machine; _or_
  * **a persistent cookie,** which remains on the user's computer/device for a defined period of time.  These types of cookies enable the platform to remember a visitor and to serve users with appropriate content while speeding up the load rate of the web page.

As for the domain to which it belongs, cookies are either:

  * **first-party cookies,** which are set by the web server of the visited page and share the same domain; or
  * **third-party cookies,** stored by a different domain to the visited page's domain. This can happen when the webpage references a file, such as JavaScript, located outside its domain.

Sena uses cookies to deliver improved functionality and to enhance your experience on our websites.

Subject to your right to reject cookies and delete them as described below, your use of our website indicates that you accept this policy.

#### **_How to control and delete cookies_**

If you want to restrict or block the cookies, you can do so in your browser settings. The ‘help’ function within your browser should generally tell you how.

The website [www.aboutcookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/) also contains general information on cookies on a wide variety of browsers.  That website describes how to delete cookies from your computer.

#### **_Cookies in emails_**

In additional to the cookies we use on our websites, we use cookies and similar technologies in some emails. These email cookies help us to understand whether recipients have opened an email and how they have interacted with it.  If you have enabled images, cookies may be set on your computer or device. Cookies may also be activated if you click on links within emails.

#### **_Making choices about cookies_**

If you do not want to accept cookies from our emails, simply close the email before downloading any images or clicking on any links. You can also set your browser to restrict or reject cookies. These settings will apply to all cookies on websites and emails.

In some instances, depending on your email or browser settings, cookies in an email may be automatically accepted (for example, if you have added an email address to your address book or safe senders list). Please check your email browser or device instructions for more information on this.

### **What We Do with Personal Information**

The information you provide, including information you voluntarily provide and the cookies you accept by using this website without disabling cookies in your browser, will be kept confidential and used to support your customer relationship with Sena. Among other things, we use this data to tailor your experience on our website. By giving us your email or other contact information, you are consenting to us sending you information about our various product upgrades, special offers, and other new products and services from Sena that we feel may be of interest to you. Only Sena or agents working on behalf of Sena (as described below) will have access to your information. If you do not want to receive such mailings, simply tell us when you give us your personal information by not checking applicable boxes that provide consent to use your information. At any time should you choose to, you could opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the opt-out section below. Sena will not share your personal information to any outside organization for its use in marketing or solicitation without your consent. Your information may be shared with agents or contractors of Sena for the purpose of performing services for Sena. For example, if we need to ship something to you, we must share your name and address with a shipping company. We only provide third party agents with the minimum amount of information needed to complete the requested service or transaction.

### **Sharing Your Information**

We share your information with third parties to help us use your information, as described above. For example, we use a third party to run our online store.  When you make a purchase or attempt to make a purchase through this website, you will be redirected to the third party store.  That site will collect certain information from you, including your name, billing address, shipping address, payment information (including credit card numbers), email address, and phone number.  We refer to that information as “Order Information.”  The third party with which we contract is entirely responsible for your Order Information.  For customer service purposes, some limited order details such as items purchased, purchase date, or other such details are shared with Sena.  However, we do not gain access to your credit card number. 

That third party uses your Order Information generally to fulfill orders initiated from this website (including processing your payment information, arranging for shipping, and providing you with invoices and/or order confirmations).  Additionally, the third party will use your Order Information to:

  * Communicate with you
  * Screen orders for potential risk or fraud
  * If you opt-in during the checkout process, the third party will share your email information with us so we may provide you with information or advertising relating to our products]

We also use Google Analytics to help us understand how our customers use this website – you can read more about how Google uses your information here: <https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/>. You can also opt-out of Google Analytics here: <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>.

Finally, we may also share your information to comply with applicable laws and regulations, to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other lawful request for information we receive, or to otherwise protect our rights.

### **Behavioral Advertising**

As described above, we use your information to provide you with targeted advertisements or marketing communications we believe may be of interest to you. For more information about how targeted advertising works, you can visit the Network Advertising Initiative’s (“NAI”) educational page at <http://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising/how-does-it-work>.

You can opt out of targeted advertising by using the links below:

  * Facebook: <https://www.facebook.com/settings/?tab=ads>
  * Google: <https://www.google.com/settings/ads/anonymous>
  * Bing: <https://advertise.bingads.microsoft.com/en-us/resources/policies/personalized-ads>
  * Twitter: <https://help.twitter.com/en/safety-and-security/privacy-controls-for-tailored-ads>
  * LinkedIn: <https://www.linkedin.com/help/linkedin/answer/62931/manage-advertising-preferences?lang=en>

Additionally, you can opt out of some of these services by visiting the Digital Advertising Alliance’s opt-out portal at: <http://optout.aboutads.info/>.

### **Your Rights**

If you are a resident of Europe, you have the right to access personal information we hold about you and to ask that your information be corrected, updated, or deleted. If you would like to exercise this right, please contact us through the contact information on this website.

Additionally, if you are a resident of Europe we note that we are processing your information in order to fulfill contracts we might have with you (for example, if you make an order of a product listed on this website), or otherwise to pursue our legitimate business interests listed above.  Additionally, please note that your information will be transferred outside of Europe, including to the United States.

### **Data Retention**

When you initiate an order from this website, our third-party vendors will maintain your Order Information unless and until you ask them or us to delete it.

### **Linked Websites**

Other sites which are linked to/from our website (including the websites of Sena affiliates) may have different policies. Since we do not control these websites, we encourage you to review the privacy policies posted on those sites for details.

### **Security Measures**

We protect the personal information you share with us. At Sena, access to your personal information is limited to people who need it to do their job. In addition, it is our policy to maintain the integrity of any personal information within our possession.

### **How to Opt-Out of Our Use of Your Personal Information**

Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter or promotional materials may opt-out of receiving these communications at any time. They may do so by clicking on the unsubscribe link at the bottom of each email.

Processing...
